bitc1.biz 2015-03-15

# BITC1 - Your Crypto Provider

An important part of the relationship we have with our Clients is the information you share with us. We want you to know how we treat your private information. BITC1 Company protects our clients' privacy and does its best to provide their safety and convenience online. The BITC1 website is subject to this Statement of Privacy. It regulates data accumulation and usage at the website. Using the BITC1 website infers your consent to the data practices given in this statement.

**Your Personal Information Accumulation**

BITC1 accumulates such personal data as your name and e-mail address.

We also need some details about your software and hardware which are collected automatically by BITC1. We receive such information as the type of your browser, your IP address, access times, domain names to maintain high level of our services and to manage the statistics of the BITC1 website. 

Please consider the fact that if you reveal your personal data directly through the public message boards of the BITC1 website, we are irresponsible for data privacy and such data can be used by third parties. We assure you that we do not read or interfere into your online private communication. 

BITC1 Statement of Privacy does not apply to other websites which you can decide to visit using a link from our website. That's why read attentively their privacy statements before giving them the right to collect your personal information. Please be aware that BITC1 does not bear responsibility for the content and rules of other websites 

**Your Personal Information Usage**

BITC1 accumulates your personal data and use it to ensure the operations on the website and to make appropriate provisions for your experience at our website. BITC1 also needs your personally identifiable data to inform you about other services or products you can obtain from BITC1 and its affiliated companies. BITC1 is also interested in your opinion and impression on potential new products and services that we may plan to offer you. In this case we may contact you via your e-mail. 

BITC1 does not share the information about its clients with other persons concerned. From time to time BITC1 may make you proposals on behalf of its business partners if the proposal seems to be interesting for you. In such cases your personal data (name, address, e-mail, telephone number) will not be revealed to them. But this information can be given to authorized persons and partners for the purpose of helping us with our responsibilities for performance of our commitments. All of such third persons understand the importance of the clients' personal privacy and they are under duty of confidentiality. 

BITC1 does not reveal such information about our client as his/her nationality, political or religious affiliations without their permission, or misuse it. 

BITC1 monitors the websites and pages which are visited by our clients within personal script system (PSS). It is necessary to define the most popular services of BITC1. This information also helps to offer customized content and to advertize within BITC1 to those customers who demonstrate interest to definite subject. 

Your private information can be revealed by BITC1 only upon the request of law-enforcement authorities or when we are sure that it is necessary for:  
* the fulfillment of laws requirement;  
* PSS property or rights protection, security and defence;  
* PSS users' personal safety protection in the cases of force majeure and hazards.

**Your Personal Information Security**

BITC1 guarantees the safety of your personal data in a safe environment and protects it from improper access, unlawful use or revealing. The use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol, protects your personal data at the time of transmission to other website (for example, when it comes to your credit card number). 

**Use of Cookies**

So-called "cookies" are used at the BITC1 website to help you in personalizing your online presence. A cookie means a text file which a web-page server places on your hard disk. Cookies pose no threat to your computer: no memory leak, virus infection or other undesirable results can be expected. Only web-server in the domain, which issued it to you, can read it, because cookies are uniquely assigned. 

One of the main purposes of cookies is saving your time, which is very convenient for you. Cookie is intended to signal the web-server that the user has returned to a particular page. For instance if you registered and personalized on the BITC1's website to use its services, the cookie is necessary for the website to recall some particular information at your following visit. The process of your personal data recording becomes simpler and easier. Such data may include billing addresses, shipping addresses, etc. When you come back to the BITC1 website again, the data you conveyed before can be restored. In this case you get quick access to the necessary BITC1 website features. 

You can accept and decline cookies as you like. Most web browsers allow cookies by default, but usually you have an ability to set your browser to reject cookies if you want to. But if you make up your mind to reject cookies, you may fail to use all the interactive features of our website to the full as well as the features of other websites. 

**Changes to This Statement**

BITC1 reserves the right to amend occasionally this Statement of Privacy to correspond actual company's and customers' interaction. BITC1strongly recommends you to review this Statement from time to time not to miss the updates. In this case you'll be always aware of BITC1 safety methods towards your personal data. 

**Contact Information**

BITC1 is glad to receive your comments concerning this Statement of Privacy. In case you think that BITC1 does not follow the rules and violate this Statement, contact BITC1 at **abuse@bitc1.biz**   
We guarantee that we will take commercially reasonable efforts to discover and solve the problem.
